下狗式是来自梵文中的"朝下  面  犬  体式"
You know, downward-facing dog comes from the Sanskrit phrase adho mukha shvanasana.
好美  是什么意思
Oh, that's beautiful. What does it mean?
"下犬式"
"Downward-facing dog."
好吧  我猜梵文里大概没有"屁股朝上头朝下"
Yeah, I guess they don't have Sanskrit for "Butts up and heads down."
印度性爱圣经可是我们写的
Hey, we wrote the Kama Sutra.
跟屁股扯上边的  我们肯定有那个词
If it involves butts, there's a word for it.
我们不是要在上班前吃早饭吗
I thought we were getting breakfast before work.
我忘了  抱歉
Oh, right, sorry.
是我的错  我邀请佩妮跟我一起做瑜伽
It's my fault. I asked Penny to do yoga with me.
如果要  我可以在五分钟内换好衣服啊
If you want, I can get ready in five minutes.
你盲目自信的样子真可爱
It's cute that you think that.
算了  没事
Don't worry about it.
我能请你帮个忙吗  能不能帮忙我去遛一下小桂子
Hey, can I ask you a favor? Would you mind taking Cinnamon for a walk?
没问题啊  你免费在这住  我当然是欠你的啦
Sure. You're living here for free.I guess I owe you.
再见啦  小桂子  你要乖啊
Bye, Cinnamon. Be a good girl.
-再见啦  小宝贝  -再见
- Yeah, bye, sweetie! - Bye!
再见  莱纳德
Yeah, yeah, bye, Leonard.
树式
Okay, and tree pose.
她"完事"了
Well, she's done.
第十季  第十九集
最近我们研发无限持续陀螺仪很顺利呢
Things have been going really well with the infinite resistance gyroscope.
那很好啊  怎么顺利
That's great. How so?
这个项目是机密  恕我不能透露
Oh, the project is classified.I can't tell you.
不过我可以把机密部分消音掉
Oh, I suppose I could redact the classified parts.
好的  我想出了一个绝妙的方法
All right, um, I came up with an elegant solution
来解决规模简化的问题
to the the reduction of scale problem.
我用了非线性动力学...
I used the nonlinear dynamics...
然后我产生的流量皮质...
And then I generated flow cortices...
使高温下的玻色爱因斯坦凝聚
...using a higher temperature Bose-Einstein condensate,
然后就成功啦
And that did it.
真好奇他们在消音什么
Wow, I wonder what they're redacting.
你怎么不问问我最近在研究什么
Why don't you ask me what I'm working on?
行啊  那你最近都在研究什么
Oh, very well. What have you been working on?
也欢迎你按喇叭消音掉无聊的部分
And feel free to honk during the boring parts.
我最近在做实验来表明人体控制肌肉的信号
I'm doing some experiments to show that the signal to move a muscle
是在大脑做出决定前就发送出去了
occurs before you know you even decided to move it.
所以你在尝试做实验找出意识在大脑中存在的位置
W... So you're attempting to pinpoint where consciousness resides in the brain.
是的  我在试着得出何处与何时
Yes, I'm trying to figure out the nanometer and the attosecond,
意识在大脑中产生  精确到纳米与原子秒
precisely where and when an event of awareness takes place.
真是没想到
Well, what do you know?
本来我还等着要受无聊生物学的轰炸
Here I was, waiting to be bored with biology,
结果却让你搔到了我求知的痒处
and instead you tickle my intellectual fancy.
而这痒处不同于我的身体  是允许被搔的
Which, unlike my body, is an okay place to tickle.
在我六岁的时候
You know, when I was six,
我想要嫁给童书《晚安大猩猩》的那大猩猩
I wanted to marry the gorilla from Good Night, Gorilla.
或许当时我有点未卜先知了
Maybe I was onto something.
先生们  刚才我跟这根汤匙发生了一件史上最有趣的事
Gentlemen, the most interesting thing just happened with this spoon.
除非它对你唱《当我们座上宾》  不然我不信
Unless it was singing "Be Our Guest," I doubt it.
《美女与野兽》中的家具仆人们唱了这首歌
我想都没想就挑了这根汤匙
Yeah, I picked it up without thinking about it.
一个神经学的问题就产生了
Which raises a neuroscientific question,
我什么时候决定了选择这根汤匙
when did I decide to pick it up?
更大的问题是  你要用那根汤匙吃什么
The bigger question is, what are you gonna eat with that spoon?
你都没拿食物
You didn't get any food.
他提的这点的确挺有意思
He does raise an interesting point.
艾米正在研究意图与意识间的时间滞差
Amy is studying the time lag between intent and awareness,
而我意识到这也能套用进量子力学里的测量问题上
and I realized that applies to the measurement problem in quantum mechanics.
我也意识到了在我说出来这话
Now, I recognize there will be a time lag
到你们用谷歌查之间也会有时间滞差  所以我等你们
between me saying that and you Googling what it means,so I'll wait.
我懂好吗  谢尔顿
I understand it, Sheldon.
我也懂
Yeah, me, too.
抱歉  我放空了  我们还在聊汤匙吗
I'm sorry, I spaced.Are we still talking about the spoon?
看到你对艾米的工作感到兴趣挺好的
It's nice to see you taking an interest in Amy's work.
别误会了
Well, don't get me wrong.
神经生物学不过就是研究灰色黏糊糊东西的科学
Neurobiology's nothing more than the science of gray squishy stuff.
但是当它跟物理学关联起来
But, you know, when it connects to physics,
给马喂好草料  师弟  咱们要直奔西天啦
gas up the Ford, Martha, we're going for a drive.
那你跟珍妮佛撕逼了吗
So did you confront Jennifer?
本来准备要  结果她请了病假
I was going to, but she called in sick.
你猜还有谁请了病假
And guess who else called in sick.
-保罗  -保罗
- Paul. - Paul.
谁是保罗啊
Who's Paul?
我们办公室圣诞派对的时候你们见过面  是南希的老公
Oh, you met him at the office Christmas party.He's married to Nancy.
那个人啊  等等  谁是南希
Oh, sure. Wait, Nancy?
我敢打赌珍妮佛能借此升职  真是太不公平了
I bet Jennifer gets a promotion out of this,which is so unfair
我比她加倍努力好吗
because I work twice as hard as she does.
别担心啦  杰瑞不会被这种小把戏所欺骗
Don't worry, Jerry won't be fooled by that type of behavior.
谁是杰瑞
Jerry?
兰迪用这招不好使  蒂娜用这招也不好使
It didn't work for Randy, it didn't work for Tina,
所以肯定珍妮佛用这招也不好使
it sure as hell isn't gonna work for Jennifer.
但愿如此吧  我只是很讨厌别人玩那种把戏
Well, I hope not.I just hate when people play those kinds of games.
谁是蒂娜
Tina?
凭你的销售记录  你根本无需担心
With your sales record, you have nothing to worry about.
我是不是去了你办公室的假圣诞派对
I went to your office Christmas party?
我喜欢上竖琴课
You know, I like harp lessons,
但我现在考虑要不要换成上电梯维修班了
but I'm thinking of switching to elevator repair lessons.
你在研究什么
What are you working on?
我刚在思考你的实验  关于决策的神经科学
I was thinking about your experiment on the neuroscience of decision making,
然后我意识到  如果将其与量子力学中的测量问题相联系
and I realized,if we connect it to the measurement problem in quantum mechanics,
我们将有机会用哥本哈根诠释
we have a chance to disprove the role of consciousness
哥本哈根诠释是量子力学的一种诠释
对意识的角色进行证伪
in the Copenhagen Interpretation.
等下  你是说如果将我的实验跟你的计算相结合
Wait, are you saying if we combine my experiment with your calculations,
我们能推断出
we can determine the precise moment in time
波函数坍缩的确切时间
when the wave function collapses?
这可能是最有创造力的组合了  之前是我把红色思乐冰混到蓝色思乐冰里
It could be the most inspired combination since I mixed red Icee into my blue Icee.
喝起来就像在喝七彩虹中的两彩
It was like drinking 2/7 of the rainbow.
谢尔顿  这真是太有意思了
Sheldon, this is really interesting.
对啊  而且这个不会把我的牙染成紫色
Yeah, and this one won't stain my teeth purple.
我们之前从未在专业领域上合作过
You know, we've never collaborated professionally before.
你不担心这可能会影响我们的关系吗
Are you worried it might affect our relationship?
这个观点非常有道理
That is a valid point.
或许我们该确立一些基本规则
Perhaps we should establish some ground rules.
那样我感觉好多了
Well, that would make me feel better.
好吧  我们现在就开始吧
All right, let's start right now.
规则一  不许用性来达到目的
Uh, rule number one,no using sexuality to get your way.
这规则真鬼扯
That's a ridiculous rule.
是咩
Is it?
好了  感觉如何
Okay, how is that?
我真的感觉到毒素被缓缓排出我的肌肤
I can actually feel the toxins being pulled out of my skin.
这是补水面膜
Well, this is a moisturizing mask.
好吧  那我真的感觉到水分源源不断地注入我的肌肤
Oh, well, then I can actually feel the moisture going into my skin.
希望你别介意  昨晚我用了一点你的眼霜
Hey, I hope you don't mind,I used a little of your eye cream last night.
怪不得某人的双眸越来越紧致明亮
I thought someone looked brighter and tighter.
我还是想知道杰瑞是谁
I'd still like to know who Jerry is.
别纠结了  要不敷完面膜
Don't worry about it. Hey, after this,
我们一起出去做点什么吧
how about we all go out and do something together?
那真是太棒了  谢谢
That would be great. Thank you.
你想去逛街吗
You want to go shopping?
好呀  爽
Ooh, yes. Fun.
或许我们可以做一些我们都喜欢的事  比如说玩桌游
Or we could do something we'll all enjoy,like play a board game.
♪ 我在想  我和你 ♪
♪ Imagine me and you, I do ♪
Happy Together - The turtles 该歌曲也常在爱情电影中出现
♪ 我日夜不停地思念你 ♪
♪ I think about you day and night ♪
♪ 唯一该做的事  是想着我心爱的女孩 ♪
♪ It's only right to think about the one you love ♪
♪ 想抱紧她 ♪
♪ And hold her tight ♪
♪ 快乐地在一起 ♪
♪ So happy together ♪
♪ 除你之外  我不会再爱上别人 ♪
♪ I can't see me lovin' nobody but you ♪
♪ 一生如此 ♪
♪ For all my life ♪
♪ 当你跟我在一起 ♪
♪ When you're with me ♪
♪ 宝贝  碧空万里 ♪
♪ Baby, the skies will be blue ♪
♪ 一生如此 ♪
♪ For all my life.♪
我已经把我们的基本规则制定出来了
I believe I've made some progress on our ground rules.
好的  都是什么
Oh, good. What are they?
规则一  跟物理有关的  我有最终决定权
Okay, uh, number one: in matters of physics, I have the final say.
跟神经科学有关的  你有最终决定权
In matters of neuroscience, you have the final say.
除非我不同意
Unless I disagree.
还有  规则二  当论文出版时  我是第一作者
Oh, here.Number two: when we publish, my name goes first.
之后如果我们获任何奖  我第一个发言
Oh, subsequently, if we win any awards, I speak first.
我不想到我发言时  因时长被乐队奏乐赶下场
I don't want to be talking when the orchestra plays us off.
-我能看看吗  -当然
-Can I see that?  -Oh, of course.
我会拿回来的
I'll get that back.
就像我所有内裤  那个本子上也写着"所有权归谢尔顿·库珀"
Like all my underwear, that notebook says "Property of Sheldon Cooper."
谢尔顿  如果我们要制定基本规则  那我告诉你第一条就是
Sheldon, if we're gonna have ground rules,I'll tell you the first ground rule.
基本规则我说了算
I make the ground rules.
我本来可以写下来  但现在不行了
I'd write that down, but I can't now, can I?
我的意思是  他们虽然什么都没说
I mean, they didn't say anything,
但我却觉得自己有点像奇怪的电灯泡
but I just kind of felt like I was being a weird third wheel.
所以你也懂那种感觉啊  有意思
Huh, so you can tell what that feels like. Interesting.
总之  我后来想我也可以跟我朋友出去也会玩得很开心的呀
Anyway, I figured I can hang out with my friends and have fun, too.
如果你对开心的定义是坐着小面包车去超市买尿布
Well, if your idea of fun is riding in a minivan to Target for diapers,
那准备好疯狂一把啦
things are about to get nuts.
我只是觉得跟乐于与我玩耍的人在一起感觉很好
Oh, it's just nice to be with people who are happy to have me around.
是不是呀  哈雷
Isn't that right, Halley?
至少有人敢于说出真相
Well, at least someone had the courage to say it.
谢谢  你真是个好市民
Thank you, you are a good citizen.
早说了吧
Told you.
去吧  把我内裤扔出窗外试试  也会有人送回来
Go ahead, throw my underwear out the window. Same thing's gonna happen.
非常好  你想听听咱俩的新规则吗
Terrific.Do you want to hear our new set of ground rules?
说吧
Fire away.
第一条  我俩是队友  而不是对手
Number one: we're on the same team,we're not in competition.
聪明  因为目前的比分可是谢尔顿赢了
That's smart, because Sheldon 1, Amy 0.
第二条  意见不同可以有礼貌地提出来
Number two: disagreements can happen politely.
不可以嘲讽别人的想法傻
There's no need to call an idea stupid.
哇  有人在上面画了个鸡鸡
Aw, someone drew a penis in it.
-你有认真听吗  -抱歉  你继续
-Are you listening?  -I'm sorry, go ahead.
第三条  为了鼓舞士气   工作期间可以适当休息
Number three.To avoid getting frustrated, we take built-in breaks
每完成一步都可以发个小奖励
and reward our successes with a small treat.
这个主意不错
Ooh, that sounds fun.
你指的是真正的奖励吧
Now, we're talking about real treats, right?
而不是我妈拿来糊弄我的圣经段子
Not Bible verses like my mother used to give me.
你想要什么都行  那我们开工吧
Whatever you want. So, shall we get to work?
生物与物理强强联合
Biology and physics coming together--
花生酱巧克力是深受北美人民喜爱的零食
我们是智商界的花生酱巧克力
this is like the peanut butter cup of the mind.
人家知道想要什么奖励了
Oh, I know what I want my treat to be!
♪ 我在想  我和你 ♪
♪ Imagine me and you, I do ♪
♪ 我日夜不停地思念你 ♪
♪ I think about you day and night ♪
♪ 唯一该做的事 ♪
♪ It's only right ♪
♪ 是想着我心爱的女孩 ♪
♪ To think about the girl you love ♪
♪ 想抱紧她 ♪
♪ And hold her tight ♪
♪ 快乐地在一起 ♪
♪ So happy together ♪
♪ 我该不该花一毛钱打给你 ♪
♪ If I should call you up, invest a dime ♪
♪ 听你说你是我的女孩 ♪
♪ And you say you belong to me ♪
♪ 让我心花怒放 ♪
♪ And ease my mind ♪
♪ 让我的世界充满欢愉 ♪
♪ Imagine how the world could be, so very fine ♪
♪ 快乐地在一起 ♪
♪ So happy together ♪
♪ 除你之外 ♪
♪ I can't see me ♪
♪ 我不会再爱上别人 ♪
♪ Lovin' nobody but you ♪
♪ 一生如此 ♪
♪ For all my life... ♪
瞧瞧
Wow, look at that.
没错  实在是叹为观止
Yes, this is remarkable.
所以我们都觉得这完全是没用的垃圾
So we're agreed: it's complete garbage.
对了  你可以当第一作者
By the way, your name can go first.
我很高兴看到他们相处融洽
I mean, I'm glad they're getting along,
但现在我开始有点不舒服了
but it's starting to make me uncomfortable.
你是担心他会成为你跟佩妮的小三吗
Well, are you worried he's like another man in her life?
有一点  直到我看到他俩穿了闺蜜装
A little, until I saw them in matching tops, so...
太好了  174片尿布  足够我们撑到周三啦
Nice. 174 diapers.That ought to get us to Wednesday.
你跟他俩聊过这件事吗
Well, have you talked to them about it?
我应该如何开口呀  "不要背着我自己玩吗"
Well, what am I supposed to say."Stop having fun without me"?
我每次出门她都要这么说
This one says that every time I go out.
看到没  我还是有听你说话
See? I listen to you.
拉杰只是和女生特别处得来
Look, Raj just gets along with women.
我知道  但他本来是我的朋友
I-I know,but he was my friend first.
她就像是偷走了我的朋友  然后两人开开心心地
It's like she's stealing him and they're just having the best time
做各种女生才做的蠢事
doing all their dumb girly stuff together.
你确定自己融不进去吗  某人听起来还挺像个小婊子啊
You sure you don't fit in? You sound like a catty bitch to me.
我不知道到底是哪里出错了
I don't know where we went wrong.
这些计算乱七八糟  我都不确定它到底通不通
Yeah, the math is so inelegant.I'm not even sure it makes sense.
别放弃  也许我们能改好
Well, don't give up. Maybe we can fix it.
能请你不要这么大声呼吸吗  我都能听到你鼻腔中的口哨声了
Can you stop breathing so loud? I can hear your nose whistling.
我还能听到你的脸猛讲屁话呢  扯平了
I can hear your face talking, so we're even.
够了  赶紧去擤鼻涕  要不就教它吹一首《康城赛马》
All right, either blow your nose or teach it to play "Camptown Races."
好  好  你想要我擤鼻涕  好  我擤了
Fine. Fine. You want me to blow my nose? Here, I'll blow it.
舒服了吧
Better?
不行  我还能听到
No, I can still hear it.
等等  是我发出的  算了别管了
Oh, wait, that's me. Never mind, it's fine.
你这个人真烦人  我就知道不该跟你一起工作
You know, you're exhausting.I knew working together was a bad idea.
等一下  我知道哪里错了
Hold on. I see what's wrong here.
我们只传送到了枕叶部分
We did the propagation only to the occipital lobe,
却忘了前额皮质
not to the prefrontal cortex.
那就代表这个延迟参数  应该再增加250毫秒
That would mean that this delayed parameter should be increased 250 milliseconds.
这样才对嘛
Oh, that is much better.
老弟  如果你的妙计能够像你的鼻涕一样喷薄而出的话
Yeah, boy, if good ideas came out of your brain the way mucus comes out of your nose,
我们就所向无敌了
we'd be in good shape.
来  喝一小口  在嘴里搅动一下
Now, take a sip, swirl it around your mouth,
用心去体会它的香气、单宁和口感
and try to notice the flavors,the tannins, the textures.
如何
Well?
我应该先把口香糖吐出来
I probably should have spit out my gum first.
你知道吗  过去的几周我过得相当艰难
Yeah. You know,the last couple of weeks have been pretty rough,
但和你们住在一起让我的心情总算轻松了一点
but, uh, staying here with you guys has really helped take my mind off of it.
我们也很喜欢你住在这里  对吧  亲爱的
Well, we've loved having you around. Right, sweetie?
-莱纳德  -他什么时候走的呀
-Leonard?  -Yeah, when did he leave?
是啊  真没礼貌
Yeah, that's rude.
跟你们一起待着感觉真好
You know, it's nice to spend time with people
你们不会把工作当成肥皂剧讨论
who don't talk about work like it's some kind of soap opera.
珍妮佛还在尝试一路"睡"上去吗
Jennifer still trying to sleep her way to the top?
是的
Yeah.
有人陪佩妮做那些你不喜欢的事  你应该高兴才对
You should be happy someone wants to do the stuff with Penny you don't want to.
对呀  我多希望有人来陪着霍华德
Yeah, I wish I had that with Howard.
什么  我逼你陪我做什么了
What? What do I make you do?
我想想  魔术用品店  《神秘博士》动漫会
Let's see, the magic store,the Doctor Who convention,
全国皮带扣收藏家见面会
the National Belt Buckle Collector's meet and greet.
邀请函上写得清清楚楚 "为快乐扣紧皮带[安全带]"
It said right there on the invitation,"Buckle up for fun."
我读时你没听不是我的错
It's not my fault you didn't listen.
我相信我是反应过度了
I'm sure I'm overreacting.
你有权有自己的感受
You're entitled to feel how you feel.
如果你不喜欢  你应该和她谈
If you don't like it, you should just talk to her.
我不想让自己像个吃醋的宝宝一样
I don't want to sound like a jealous baby.
那也许你不应该和她谈
Oh, then maybe you shouldn't talk to her.
我就感觉你用错了计算模型
You know, I had a feeling you were using the wrong computational model,
但我什么也没说  因为你太敏感了
but I didn't say anything 'cause you're so sensitive.
就因为光热声味  以及鸟儿看我的样子
Just because I am easily bothered by light, heat, sound, smell
很容易让我心烦  并不代表我很敏感
and the way birds look at me does not mean I'm sensitive!
如果视觉皮质在看到动作电位时
I wonder what kind of success we'd have
我们便马上明确度量
if we defined measurement as the first moment
我们现在会取得怎样的成功呢
that an action potential is seen by the visual cortex.
这是大胆又具深刻见解的解决方案
That is a daring and insightful solution.
我们终于有进展了  真希望不吵架就能做到就好了
We're finally making progress.I wish we could do it without fighting.
如果吵架是我们获得进展的原因呢
What if the fighting is the reason we're making progress?
我想也不是可能
I suppose it's conceivable that
我们体内"战或逃"反应相关的荷尔蒙
the hormones associated with our fight-or-flight response
可以令我们的认知过程更敏锐
could be sharpening our cognitive processes.
如果是这样的话
Well, if that's the case,
你阿公阿嬷口齿不清  弯腰驼背老罗锅
then your grandparents mumble and have bad posture.
你好大的胆子  这样说我的奶奶
How dare you speak that way about my Grammy--
等等  慢着
Hey, wait a second. Wait.
ΔΤ=α0
Delta "T" could equal alpha sub-zero.
看来我们得做出选择
It seems we have a choice to make.
以科学的名义  放弃所有基本规则
Abandon all ground rules in the name of science,
或是为了我们的恋情放弃合作
or... give up collaborating for the sake of our relationship.
只有一个明确的选择
There's only one clear choice.
-科学  -不是  你这个傻逼
- Science it is. - No, you bonehead!
骂人  太好了
Name-calling, that is perfect.
我在计算这个方程式时  尽管痛骂我  知道吗
Now, when I get to this equation here, really let me have it. You know?
提示下  我穿衣服没啥品味
I-If it helps, I'm not the sharpest dresser.
总之  我知道这样很傻
Anyway, I know it's silly,
但拉杰搬来后  我觉得受到了排挤
but since Raj moved in,I've been feeling a little left out.
亲爱的  你是在说什么疯话
Well, sweetie, that's crazy.
不  佩妮  别无视他的感受
No, no, Penny, don't dismiss his feelings.
-谢谢你  我只是觉得...  -等等
-Thank you. I just feel...  -Hang on,
我不是说  他的感受不疯狂
I'm not saying that his feelings aren't crazy.
我只是不想让他觉得这里不是能安心分享的场所
I just don't want him to think that this isn't a safe place.
说实话
Well, to be truthful...
这里为什么会不能安心
Well, why wouldn't this be a safe place? I mean,
他身边有他的老婆和死党之一
he's surrounded by his wife and one of his best friends.
-我不想乱揣测莱纳德的想法  -谢谢你  我...
-I don't want to speak for Leonard.  -Thank you. I...
但当你没安全感时
But when you're insecure,
再多的外部肯定也没法让你觉得安心
no amount of external validation can ever make you feel safe.
你说得对
Yeah, you're right. You know,
你对这类的事真的很敏感
you're really sensitive about this kind of stuff.
-我善于倾听  -对
- I'm a good listener. - Yeah.
孪生姐妹花
Hey, Olsen twins...
-怎么了  -这样
-What?  -Well,
我就坐在这里  你们在讨论我的感受
I-I mean, I'm sitting right here. You're talking about my feelings
却把我晾在一边不理我
and somehow leaving me out of the conversation.
对不起  你想说什么
I'm sorry. What did you want to say?
我不知道  你们差不多都说到了
I don't know, you pretty much covered it.
你读一下好吗
Can you read them back?
"修订版基本规则第一条
"Revised ground rule number one:
我们是一队的  但这是竞争"
We are on the same team, but it is a competition."
非常好  非常好
Excellent. Excellent.
关于这点  你输定了  废柴
And on a related point, you're going down, punk.
"修订版基本规则第二条
"Revised ground rule number two:
世上绝对有愚蠢的问题
There are definitely stupid questions.
问出愚蠢的问题的人  对方可以当着其愚蠢的面指出"
And those who ask them can be told so right to their stupid face."
我喜欢这条
I love that one.
谢谢你  宝贝
Thanks, babe.
"第三条  合适的辱骂话题包括
"Number three: Fair topics for insult include
教育门第  科学领域  智力能力  以及母亲"
Educational pedigree, scientific field,intellectual prowess, and mamas."
这几点也太猛了
Yeah, that list is strong.
就像你老母渴望和水手们乱搞的欲望一样猛
Like your mother's urge to be promiscuous with sailors.